Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records - Addendum E
Yale University Divinity School Library
United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records - Addendum E
1968-2001
RG 11E
Yale University Divinity School Library
12
(25 boxes)
This record group represents a continuation of the official archives of the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia, supplementing and overlapping the papers in record groups 11, 11A, 11B, 11C, and 11D. It provides extensive information about the institutions and projects to which the United Board lent its support. The United Board for Chrisian Higher Education in Asia supports educational work in China, India, Indonesia, Japan, Korea, Myanmar, The Philippines, Republic of China (Taiwan), Thailand, and Vietnam. The United Board was established to support and coordinate the activities of Protestant colleges and universities in China. Following the Communist takeover of China, the United Board focused its efforts on educational work in other Asian nations.
United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia
Conditions Governing Access
Open to qualified researchers
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the UBCHEA
Biographical / Historical
Detailed information about the work of the United Board for Christian Higher Education during the earlier portion of the period represented by these archives is contained in Paul Lauby's book Sailing on Winds of Change: Two Decades in the Life of the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia, 1969-1990.
Scope and Contents
I. Committee Records
II. Correspondence
III. Financial Records
IV. Programs and Colleges
The files have been maintained as sent by the United Board.
Arrangement
I. Committee Records
II. Correspondence
III. Financial Records
IV. Programs and Colleges
Religious education -- Asia; Universities and colleges -- Asia; Educators; United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia
- Committee Records, 1991-92; Series I
  - Asian Trustees and Principal's Consultation, India, 1991-92 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Development of Committee Agendas and Minutes, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee of UB, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Finance/Administration Committee, 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Investment Committee, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Nominations, Committee Minutes Agenda, etc., 1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Program Policy Committee, 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Social Responsibility for Investments Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Women's Concerns Committee, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Correspondence Files, 1992-1993; Series II
  - ACUCA Project Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Asian Women Institute, 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Barrett, Dr./Mrs. S. Edward, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Bovenkerk, Dr. Henry, 1980-1997 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Brown, Dr. Russell E., 1980-1994 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Burkholder, Dr. S. Lawrence, 1983-1995 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Calder, George, 1980-1997 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Carle, Dr./Mrs. Kenneth, 1980-1986 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Carle, Robert, 1980-1994 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Charlton, Kathy, 1989-1994 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - CEAIE, 1988-1994 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Chaiyasate, Prof. Chachawan / Mrs. Somsri, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Chandi, Dr. P.T., 1980-1995 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Chiang, Nora Lan-hung, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Chung, Dr. and Mrs. Daihyun, 1986-1993 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Chung, H.S. M.D., 1980-1994 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - CCHRP, 1981-1991 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Colvin, Robert and Ruth, 1987-1994 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Community Church of Great Neck, 1980-1992 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Davidson College, 1980-1989 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Dolben, David, 1980-1992 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Dorrill, William, 1981-1990 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Fenn, Dr. William, 1980-1997 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Freeman, Mansfield, 1979-1993 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Gamble, Mrs. Sidney (Elizabeth), 1980-1990 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Gibbons, Mrs. Anne T., 1981-1990 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Goodwin, Rev. Charles, 1980-1996 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Horn, Dr. Francis, 1980-1993 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Hunt, Dr. Chester, 1980-1991 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Jayasuriya, Nalini, 1980-1991 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Jayasuriya, Nalini, 1991-1995 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Jones, Dr. Tracey, 1980-1988 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Judd, Dr. and Mrs. Walter, 1980-1992 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Kanalebe, Herman, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Lazarus, Dr. Barbara, 1987-1992 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Lee, Mrs. Shangu, 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Liu, Dr. James, 1980-1993 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Loh, I-to and Hui-chin, 1981-1994 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Lynchburg College in Virginia, 1985-1992 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - McClure, Dr. and Mrs. Robert, 1981-1991 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - McKaughan, Dr. Howard P., 1987-1992 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Mennonite Central Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Mennonite Press, 1986-1991 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Miao Hua-lun, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Moon, Dr. Beverly, 1986-1994 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Muramatsu, Yasuko, 1981-1991 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Najarian, Dr. Nishan, 1986-1990 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Nepal--United Mission to Nepal, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - O'Hare, Rev. Joseph (S.J.), 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Pearson, Mrs. Dorothy, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Presidents' and Academic Deans' Tour of China, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Rayne, Dr. Robert, 1981-1992 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Rhee, Dr. Syngman, 1980-1993 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Rossman, Dr. and Mrs. Parker, 1981-1991 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Sanders, Dr. Albert, 1980-1987 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Scheid, Mr. and Mrs. Robert, 1980-1987 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Scherbacher, Mr. Marcus W., 1984-1990 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Severinghaus, Dr. and Mrs. Leslie, 1980-1992 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Smith, Karen H., 1979-1992 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Stony Point Conference Center, 1980-1991 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Sung, Dr. Baik Nam, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Turner, James D. And Sara M., 1980-1991 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Tweedy, Mr. and Mrs. Gordon B., 1980-1993 (Box 6, Folder 75)
- Financial Records, 1990-1991; Series III
  - Financial Statements, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 75b)
  - Financial Statements, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 75a)
- Programs and Colleges, Series IV
  - China
    - Visiting Scholars
      - Di, Ms. Ganzhi, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 76)
      - Li, Ms. Yan, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 77)
      - Ma, Mr. Min, 1988-1992 (Box 6, Folder 78)
      - Yang, Ms. Zhi, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 79)
      - Yue, Prof. Mei-yun, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 80)
      - Zhang, Xiolin [file missing] (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Visiting Professors
      - Carle, Dr. Robert, 1989-1992 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Colleges and Organizations
      - AN-AZ, 1988-1997 (Box 6, Folder 83)
      - Beijing Foreign Studies University, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 84)
      - Beijing Foreign Studies University, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 84a)
      - Beijing Foreign Studies University, 1989-1995 (Box 7, Folder 84b)
      - Beijing Foreign Studies University, 1988-1990 (Box 7, Folder 84c)
      - Beijing Foreign Studies University, 1989-1998 (Box 7, Folder 84)
      - Beijing Foreign Studies University, 1988-1993 (Box 7, Folder 84e)
      - Beijing Normal University, 1988-1991 (Box 7, Folder 85)
      - China: Bridge to China, 1988-1990 (Box 7, Folder 86)
      - China: CA-CHA, 1988-1994 (Box 7, Folder 87)
      - Canada-China Program, 1987-1996 (Box 7, Folder 88)
      - Capital Normal University, 1987-1992 (Box 8, Folder 89)
      - Center for U.S.-China Arts Exchange, 1990-1992 (Box 8, Folder 90)
      - CHAO-CHIZ, 1988-1994 (Box 8, Folder 91)
      - China (A-Z), 1991-1997 (Box 8, Folder 94)
      - Chinese (A-Z), 1989-1992 (Box 8, Folder 92)
      - Chinese Academy of Social Science, 1991-1997 (Box 8, Folder 93)
      - Chinese Education Association for International Exchange, 1989-1993 (Box 8, Folder 95)
      - CEAIE: 1991 Memo of University, 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 98)
      - CEAIE: International Conference, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 96)
      - CEAIE: State Education Committee, 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 97)
      - CHO-COM, 1988-1995 (Box 8, Folder 99)
      - Deng Guang-Yu, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 100)
      - East China Normal University, 1988-1991 (Box 9, Folder 101)
      - East China Normal University, 1989-1992 (Box 9, Folder 102)
      - EUR-EZ, 1980-1991 (Box 9, Folder 103)
      - Ginling Women's College: General Correspondence, 1981-1996 (Box 9, Folder 104)
      - Goshen College, 1988-1994 (Box 9, Folder 105)
      - GU-GRA, 1988-1991 (Box 9, Folder 106)
      - GRE-GZ, 1989-1997 (Box 9, Folder 107)
      - Hangzhou University, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 108)
      - HAS-HEL, 1982-1997 (Box 9, Folder 109)
      - HEM-HIS, 1989-1992 (Box 9, Folder 110)
      - HOH-HOU, 1988-1992 (Box 9, Folder 111)
      - HSE-HUA, 1985-1991 (Box 9, Folder 112)
      - Huazhong Teachers University, 1988-1992 (Box 10, Folder 115)
      - HUB-HZ, 1988-1992 (Box 10, Folder 116)
      - Hwa Nan Women's College, 1989-1992 (Box 9, Folder 113)
      - Hwa Nan Women's College, 1989-1991 (Box 9, Folder 114)
      - Jilin Normal University, 1987-1991 (Box 10, Folder 117)
      - JOK-JZ, 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 118)
      - KA-KEY, 1988-1996 (Box 10, Folder 119)
      - KLA-KZ, 1984-1993 (Box 10, Folder 120)
      - LA-LEE, 1988-1992 (Box 10, Folder 121)
      - LEF-KUN, 1988-1997 (Box 10, Folder 122)
      - LI, 1988-1991 (Box 10, Folder 123)
      - MC, 1988-1993 (Box 10, Folder 124)
      - ME-MIZ, 1988-1992 (Box 10, Folder 125)
      - NA-NAZ, 1980-1991 (Box 10, Folder 126)
      - Nanjing University, 1986-1992 (Box 11, Folder 131a)
      - Nanjing University, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 131)
      - Nanjing University, 1991-1993 (Box 11, Folder 132)
      - Nanjing University: College English Teachers Training, 1989-1993 (Box 10, Folder 130)
      - Nanjing University: English Center, 1977-1991 (Box 11, Folder 130a)
      - Nankai University, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 133)
      - NCC Related Programs, 1990-1998 (Box 10, Folder 129)
      - NEA-NOG, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 127)
      - NOH-NZ, 1988-1992 (Box 10, Folder 128)
      - Northeast Normal University, 1986-1993 (Box 11, Folder 134)
      - OA-OLD, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 135)
      - Oberlin Shansi Memorial, 1988-1993 (Box 12, Folder 136)
      - PA-PAZ, 1988-1994 (Box 12, Folder 137)
      - POH-PZ, 1988-1991 (Box 12, Folder 138)
      - Princeton-China Christian College Archival Project, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 139)
      - RA-REZ, 1988-1994 (Box 12, Folder 140)
      - RHA-RUT, 1980-1994 (Box 12, Folder 141)
      - SA-SCY, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 142)
      - SE-SHAN, 1988-1996 (Box 12, Folder 143)
      - Shaanxi Teachers University, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 144)
      - Shaanxi Teachers University: Equipment, 1987-1994 (Box 12, Folder 145)
      - Shanghai, 1988-1993 (Box 12, Folder 146)
      - Shant-Shz, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 147)
      - Sichuan Union University: Correspondence, 1989-1994 (Box 13, Folder 148)
      - Sichuan Union University: Correspondence, 1987-1992 (Box 13, Folder 148a)
      - Sichuan Union University: Equipment, 1988-1992 (Box 13, Folder 149)
      - SO-SQU, 1988-1995 (Box 13, Folder 150)
      - Southwest China Teachers: Proposal for Scholars, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 151a)
      - STA-STO, 1988-1997 (Box 13, Folder 151)
      - STR-SZ, 1988-1996 (Box 13, Folder 152)
      - Suzhai University Projects, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 153)
      - Tibet--International Fund for Development: Ms. Ciringh Yangzen, 1987-1994 (Box 13, Folder 154)
      - TRA-TZ, 1988-1993 (Box 14, Folder 155)
      - UM-UN, 1988-1994 (Box 14, Folder 156)
      - University of Hawaii / PRC Journalists, 1985-1994 (Box 14, Folder 157)
      - University of Toronto, Canada: Centre for Religious Studies, 1989-1993 (Box 14, Folder 158)
      - University of Washington Conf. On Sino-Tibetan Languages and Linguistics, 1983-1990 (Box 14, Folder 159)
      - University of Wisconsin Boxers Conference, 1988-1993 (Box 14, Folder 160)
      - WA-WAZ, 1984-1992 (Box 14, Folder 161)
      - Wang...A to Z, 1988-1994 (Box 14, Folder 162)
      - WE-WEZ, 1985-1995 (Box 14, Folder 163)
      - WI-WIZ, 1989-1992 (Box 14, Folder 164)
      - WO-WOZ, 1988-1992 (Box 14, Folder 165)
      - Wuhan University, 1984-1993 (Box 14, Folder 166)
      - Xiamen University--Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 15, Folder 173)
      - Xiamen University, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 174)
      - Xiamen University, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 175)
      - Xiong...A to Z, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 176)
      - XO-XU, 1986-1996 (Box 15, Folder 177)
      - Xu and Xue...A to Z, 1989-1995 (Box 15, Folder 178)
      - YA-YI, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 179)
      - Yale-China Assoc., 1991 (Box 15, Folder 180)
      - Yanbian University: Correspondence, 1986-1992 (Box 16, Folder 184)
      - Yanbian University Correspondence, 1988-1993 (Box 16, Folder 183)
      - Yanbian University Geography Project, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 182)
      - Yanbian University Geography Project, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 181)
      - Yanbian University: Korean Studies Conference, 1989-1993 (Box 16, Folder 185)
      - ZHE-ZHU, 1988-1993 (Box 16, Folder 186)
      - Zhejiang University Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 16, Folder 187)
      - Zhengzhou University, 1991-1993 (Box 16, Folder 188)
      - Zhongshan University: Correspondence--Don Snow, 1985-1993 (Box 16, Folder 189)
  - India
    - Madras Christian College Proposals, 1986-1989 (Box 17, Folder 192)
    - Madras Christian College Proposals, Reports, Misc., 1991-1993 (Box 17, Folder 193)
    - St. Xavier's College Correspondence, 1991-1997 (Box 17, Folder 190)
    - St. Xavier's College: School reports, newspaper clippings, info. About school seminar, 1992-1995 (Box 17, Folder 191)
  - Indonesia
    - Indonesia--General Correspondence and Info., 1984-1992 (Box 17, Folder 194)
    - Petra Christian University: Correspondence of Dr. Wasis, rector, 1988-1992 (Box 17, Folder 195)
    - Petra Christian University: Correspondence of Dr. Wasis, rector, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 196)
    - Petra Christian University: General Correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box 17, Folder 197)
    - Petra Christian University: General Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 17, Folder 198)
    - Petra Christian University: Grant Correspondence, 1987-1993 (Box 17, Folder 199)
    - Petra Christian University: Proposals, Grants, Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 200)
    - Petra Christian University: Proposals, Grants, Correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box 17, Folder 201)
    - Satya Wacana University: General Correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 21, Folder 259)
    - Satya Wacana Christian University: Grants, Proposals, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 260)
    - Satya Wacana Christian University: Grants, Proposals, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 261)
  - Japan
    - International Christian University: Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 202)
    - International Christian University: Correspondence, 1989-1994 (Box 18, Folder 203)
    - International Christian University: Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 18, Folder 205)
    - International Christian University: Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 208)
    - International Christian University: Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 206)
    - International Christian University: Forum Report, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 216)
    - International Christian University: Info. For English-speaking applicants to ICU, ICU data, ICU magazine, info. About the service/earning program at ICU, 1996-2001 (Box 18, Folder 204)
    - International Christian University: Institute of Asian Cultural Studies Correspondence--"Asia in Transition" Symposium, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 220)
    - International Christian University: Project Reports, 1993-1995 (Box 18, Folder 217)
    - International Christian University: Project Reports and Grant Proposals, 1994-1997 (Box 18, Folder 218)
    - International Christian University: Project Reports and Project/Grant Proposals, 1992-1995 (Box 18, Folder 219)
    - International Christian University: Proposals / Evaluations of Projects, 1989-1992 (Box 18, Folder 210)
    - International Christian University: Proposal, Grants, Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 211)
    - International Christian University: Proposals, Grants, etc., 1991 (Box 18, Folder 207)
    - International Christian University: Proposals and Grants, 1993-1995 (Box 18, Folder 209)
    - International Christian University--American School in Japan: Brochures and Publications Relating to AMS, 1980-1994 (Box 18, Folder 215)
    - International Christian University--American School in Japan: Correspondence, 1991-1996 (Box 18, Folder 214)
    - International Christian University Foundation: Correspondence-- Foundation, Grants, etc., 1981-1998 (Box 18, Folder 212)
    - International Christian University Foundation: Luncheon Programs (Women's Committee Foundation), 1983-1986 (Box 18, Folder 213)
    - Kwansei Gakuin University: General Correspondence, 1983-85 (Box 18, Folder 221)
    - Kwansei Gakuin University: General Correspondence, 1986-1991 (Box 18, Folder 222)
    - Sophia University: Correspondence, 1987-1992 (Box 19, Folder 225)
    - Sophia University: Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 19, Folder 226)
    - Sophia University and Tokyo Woman's Christian University: Proposals and Grants, 1990-1992 (Box 18, Folder 223)
    - Tokyo Woman's Christian University: Proposals and Grants, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 224)
  - Korea
    - Korea: General Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 227)
    - Ewha Woman's University: Correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box 20, Folder 239)
    - Ewha University: Korean Women's Institute, 1992-1994 (Box 20, Folder 240)
    - Ewha Woman's University: Proposals, Grants, etc., 1990-1994 (Box 20, Folder 237)
    - Ewha Woman's University: Proposals, Grants, etc., 1991-1993 (Box 20, Folder 238)
    - Han Nam University: Correspondence, 1986-1992 (Box 19, Folder 231)
    - Han Nam University: Correspondence, 1989-1996 (Box 19, Folder 233)
    - Han Nam University: President Dr. Won Sul Lee, Taejon, Korea, Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 228)
    - Han Nam University: President Dr. Won Sul Lee, Taejon, Korea, Correspondence, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 229)
    - Han Nam University: President Dr. Won Sul Lee, Taejon, Korea, Correspondence, 1988-99 (Box 19, Folder 230)
    - Han Nam University: Proposals, Grants, Etc., 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 232)
    - Han Nam University: Proposals/Grants, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 234)
    - Han Nam University: Proposals/Grants, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 235)
    - Han Nam University: Publications, Reports, Printed Matter, 1980-1993 (Box 19, Folder 236)
    - Seoul Woman's University: Dr. Chung Koo-Young, President-- Correspondence, 1983-1997 (Box 20, Folder 242)
    - Seoul Woman's University: Proposals/Grants, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 241)
    - Sogang University: Rev. Park Hong, President--Correspondence, 1989-1993 (Box 20, Folder 243)
    - Sogang University: General Correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box 20, Folder 244)
    - Sogang University: Project Report, 1992-1994 (Box 20, Folder 247)
    - Sogang University: Proposals, Grants, Etc., 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 245)
    - Sogang University: Proposals, Grants, Reports, 1991-1994 (Box 20, Folder 246)
    - Soong Sil University: Project Report, 1992-1994 (Box 21, Folder 251)
    - Soong Sil University: Project Report, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 250)
    - Soong Sil University: Proposals, Grants, Etc., 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 249)
    - Soong Sil University: Proposals, Grants, Etc., 1991-1995 (Box 20, Folder 248)
    - Yonsei University: Alumni Association of New York / New Jersey, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 254)
    - Yonsei University: Correspondence--General/Misc., 1968-1994 (Box 21, Folder 257)
    - Yonsei University: Correspondence, 1980-1993 (Box 21, Folder 256)
    - Yonsei University: Correspondence: Dr. Young Sik Park, President, 1988-1992 (Box 21, Folder 255)
    - Yonsei University: Medical Center, 1991-1994 (Box 21, Folder 252)
    - Yonsei University: Medical Center 1995 Scholarship (Box 21, Folder 253)
    - Yonsei University: Project Report, 1992-1994 (Box 21, Folder 258)
  - Myanmar
    - Myanmar Institute of Theology: Correspondence, 1990-1996 (Box 21, Folder 262)
  - Philippines
    - Asian School of Music, Worship, and the Arts (formerly: Asian Institute of Liturgy and Music), 1990-1992 (Box 21, Folder 263)
    - ACSC: Proposals, Grants, Etc. Association of Christian Schools and Colleges, 1988-1993 (Box 21, Folder 264)
    - Brokenshire College: CREATE-UCCP--Proposals, 1991-1994 (Box 22, Folder 267)
    - Brokenshire College: Project B--Grants, Proposals, 1989-1993 (Box 22, Folder 265)
    - Brokenshire College: Dr. Marcello P. Satentes (President): Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 22, Folder 266)
    - Central Philippine University, Dr. Agustin Pulido (President), 1987-1990 (Box 22, Folder 268)
    - De La Salle University, 1987-1993 (Box 22, Folder 271)
    - De La Salle University: China Studies Program, 1991-1993 (Box 22, Folder 270)
    - De La Salle University: Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 269)
    - Inter-Institutional Consortium: Project Reports, 1989-1992 (Box 22, Folder 272)
    - Inter-Institutional Consortium: Proposals, Grants, 1990-1993 (Box 22, Folder 273)
    - Northern Christian College: Correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box 22, Folder 274)
    - Northern Christian College: Grants, Proposals, and Reports, 1991-1993 (Box 23, Folder 275)
    - Philippine Christian University: Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 23, Folder 276)
    - Philippine Christian University: Proposals/Grants, 1989-1991 (Box 23, Folder 277)
    - Philippine Christian University: Proposals/Grants, 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 278)
    - Silliman University: General Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 23, Folder 280)
    - Silliman University: Situation, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 281)
    - Southern Christian College: Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 279)
    - Southern Christian College: Grants, Proposals, Etc., 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 282)
    - Trinity College: Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 24, Folder 283)
    - Trinity College: Grants Program, 1988-1991 (Box 24, Folder 284)
    - Trinity College of Quezon City: Proposals, Grants, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 285)
    - Trinity College of Quezon City: Proposals, Grants, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 286)
    - Trinity College of Quezon City: Proposals, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 287)
    - Create-UCCP Philipines: Correspondence, Etc., 1988 (Box 24, Folder 288)
    - Create-UCCP: Project Reports, 1991-1993 (Box 24, Folder 289)
    - Union Christian College: Proposals/Grants, 1991-1996 (Box 24, Folder 290)
  - Taiwan
    - General Correspondence: Taiwan, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 291)
    - Ginling Girls' High School, 1980-1994 (Box 24, Folder 292)
    - National Taiwan University, 1989-1994 (Box 24, Folder 293)
    - Soochow University, 1987-1993 (Box 24, Folder 294)
    - Soochow University, 1990-1994 (Box 25, Folder 296)
    - Soochow University, 1993-1995 (Box 25, Folder 295)
    - Soochow University: Custodial Fund, 1989-1991 (Box 25, Folder 297)
    - Soochow University, Friends of, 1980-1993 (Box 25, Folder 298)
    - Soochow University: Grants/Proposals, 1998-2001 (Box 25, Folder 299)
    - Tianan Theological College and Seminary: President Dr. Chang Te-Shiong, 1986-1992 (Box 25, Folder 300)
    - Tunghai University, 1986-1994 (Box 25, Folder 302)
    - Tunghai University, 1990-1994 (Box 25, Folder 301)
    - Tunghai University: Alumni, 1992-1995 (Box 25, Folder 303)
    - Tunghai University: President Dr. Ko-wang Mei, 1987-1992 (Box 25, Folder 304)
    - Tunghai University: Project Reports, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 305)
  - Thailand
    - Payap University: Grants and Proposals, 1988-1994 (Box 25, Folder 306)